{"data":[{"question":"I ______ (know) the result in a week.","a":"shall know","b":"will know","c":"a & b","answer":"3","explain":"- We use the future simple tense to talk about the future","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"6"},{"question":"It ______ (matter) if I don't come home till morning?","a":"will matter","b":"shall matter","c":"a & b","answer":"1","explain":"- We use the conditional sentence type I","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"6"},{"question":"You ______ (be) able to drive after another five lessons.","a":"shall be","b":"will be","c":"a & b","answer":"2","explain":" - The future simple tense: used to talk about the future","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"6"},{"question":"He ______ (lend) it to you if you ask him.","a":"shall lend","b":"will lend","c":"a & b","answer":"2","explain":"- We use the conditional sentence type I","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"6"},{"question":"I wonder how many of us still ______ (be) here next year.","a":"shall be","b":"will be","c":"a & b","answer":"3","explain":"- We use the future simple tense when we wonder about something in the future","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"6"},{"question":"If you think it over you ______ (see) that I am right.","a":"shall see","b":"will see","c":"a & b","answer":"2","explain":"- We use the conditional sentence type I","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"6"},{"question":"He ______ (mind) if I bring my dog?","a":"Shall he mind","b":"Will he mind","c":"a & b","answer":"2","explain":"- We use the conditional sentence type I ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"6"},{"question":"You ______ (feel) better when you've had a meal.","a":"shall feel","b":"will feel","c":"a & b","answer":"2","explain":"- We use the future simple tense when we talk about the future","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"6"},{"question":"If you leave your roller skates on the path someone ______ (fall) over them.","a":"shall fall","b":"will fall","c":"a & b","answer":"2","explain":"- We use the conditional sentence type I ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"6"},{"question":"If they fall over them and hurt themselves they ______ (sue) you.","a":"shall sue","b":"will sue","c":"a & b","answer":"2","explain":"- We use the conditional sentence type I","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"6"}]}